{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"an acute ischemic stroke.",
					"obstruction of the airway.",
					"a cardiac dysrhythmia.",
					"severe blunt trauma."
				],
				"question": "Most prehospital cardiac arrests in adults occur as the result of:",
				"source": "See Automated External Defibrillation"
			},
			"back": "a cardiac dysrhythmia."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"insert an oropharyngeal airway.",
					"suction the patient’s oropharynx",
					"increase the rate of ventilation.",
					"reposition the patient’s airway"
				],
				"question": "If gastric distention begins to make positive-pressure ventilation difficult, you should:",
				"source": "See Opening the Airway and Providing Artificial Ventilation"
			},
			"back": "reposition the patient’s airway"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"30:2",
					"5:1",
					"15:2",
					"3:1"
				],
				"question": "What is the correct ratio of compressions to ventilations when performing two-rescuer child CPR?",
				"source": "See Infant and Child CPR"
			},
			"back": "15:2"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"in patients who are intubated.",
					"if you ventilate a patient too quickly.",
					"when the airway is completely obstructed.",
					"when you deliver minimal tidal volume."
				],
				"question": "Gastric distention will MOST likely occur:",
				"source": "See Opening the Airway and Providing Artificial Ventilation"
			},
			"back": "if you ventilate a patient too quickly."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is delivered by computer.",
					"occurs every 24 months.",
					"involves hands-on practice.",
					"is self-paced and brief."
				],
				"question": "CPR retraining is the MOST effective when it:",
				"source": "See Education and Training for the EMT"
			},
			"back": "involves hands-on practice."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"femoral",
					"carotid",
					"brachial",
					"radial"
				],
				"question": "When assessing the pulse of an unresponsive infant, you should palpate the ________ artery.",
				"source": "See Infant and Child CPR"
			},
			"back": "brachial"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"horizontal.",
					"prone.",
					"supine.",
					"on a firm surface."
				],
				"question": "CPR will NOT be effective if the patient is:",
				"source": "See Positioning the Patient"
			},
			"back": "prone."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Tongue–jaw lift",
					"Head tilt–chin lift",
					"Jaw-thrust",
					"Head tilt–neck lift"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following maneuvers should be used to open a patient’s airway when a spinal injury is suspected?",
				"source": "See Opening the Airway and Providing Artificial Ventilation"
			},
			"back": "Jaw-thrust"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"start CPR and transport immediately.",
					"determine if he has a valid living will.",
					"withhold CPR until he is defibrillated.",
					"begin CPR until an AED is available."
				],
				"question": "A 60-year-old man is found to be unresponsive, pulseless, and apneic. You should:",
				"source": "See One-Rescuer Adult CPR"
			},
			"back": "begin CPR until an AED is available."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"no greater than 100 compressions per minute.",
					"at least 120 compressions per minute.",
					"80 to 100 compressions per minute.",
					"100 to 120 compressions per minute."
				],
				"question": "To ensure that you will deliver the appropriate number of chest compressions during one-rescuer adult CPR, you should compress the patient’s chest at a rate of:",
				"source": "See One-Rescuer Adult CPR"
			},
			"back": "100 to 120 compressions per minute."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"blind finger sweeps.",
					"bag-mask ventilation.",
					"abdominal thrusts.",
					"back slaps."
				],
				"question": "Initial treatment to dislodge a severe foreign body airway obstruction in a responsive infant involves:",
				"source": "See Foreign Body Airway Obstruction in Infants and Children"
			},
			"back": "back slaps."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"greater than 2.4 inches",
					"between 1 inch and 2 inches",
					"at least 2 inches",
					"at least 1 inch"
				],
				"question": "When performing chest compressions on an adult, the EMT should compress:",
				"source": "See Elements of BLS"
			},
			"back": "at least 2 inches"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"has a pulse but is unresponsive and breathing shallowly.",
					"has experienced trauma but is breathing effectively.",
					"is semiconscious, injured, and breathing adequately.",
					"is unresponsive, uninjured, and breathing adequately."
				],
				"question": "A patient should be placed in the recovery position when he or she:",
				"source": "See Opening the Airway and Providing Artificial Ventilation"
			},
			"back": "is unresponsive, uninjured, and breathing adequately."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"100",
					"110",
					"90",
					"120"
				],
				"question": "What is the minimum number of chest compressions that should be delivered per minute to a 4-month-old infant?",
				"source": "See Infant and Child CPR"
			},
			"back": "100"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"rib fractures.",
					"a fractured sternum.",
					"gastric distention.",
					"liver laceration."
				],
				"question": "Complications associated with chest compressions include all of the following, EXCEPT:",
				"source": "See Check for Breathing and a Pulse"
			},
			"back": "gastric distention."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"15:2.",
					"5:1.",
					"5:2.",
					"30:2."
				],
				"question": "In two-rescuer adult CPR, you should deliver a compression to ventilation ratio of:",
				"source": "See Two-Rescuer Adult CPR"
			},
			"back": "30:2."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"until a radial pulse is felt.",
					"80 to 100 times per minute.",
					"to a depth of 1 to 2 inches.",
					"with one or two hands."
				],
				"question": "When performing CPR on a child, you should compress the chest:",
				"source": "See Infant and Child CPR"
			},
			"back": "with one or two hands."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"severe chest trauma.",
					"respiratory arrest.",
					"a cardiac dysrhythmia.",
					"a drug overdose."
				],
				"question": "In most cases, cardiopulmonary arrest in infants and children is caused by:",
				"source": "See Infant and Child CPR"
			},
			"back": "respiratory arrest."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Chest compressions",
					"Cardiac monitoring",
					"Abdominal thrusts",
					"Automated defibrillation"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following is NOT a BLS intervention?",
				"source": "See Elements of BLS"
			},
			"back": "Cardiac monitoring"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-14-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Abdominal thrusts",
					"Finger sweeps",
					"Chest thrusts",
					"Back slaps"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following techniques should you use to dislodge a foreign body airway obstruction in a patient who is in an advanced stage of pregnancy or who is very obese?",
				"source": "See Foreign Body Airway Obstruction in Adults"
			},
			"back": "Chest thrusts"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-14",
		"label": "Chapter 14"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}